Changelog 2.4.1
(Compiled 17-Oct-2010)

Fixed Ticker auction/maxCounterTime glitch
Fixed general CSS Bugs
Corrected missing Rewards link
Corrected malformed Admin Panel menu
Improved image caching
Improved licensing and fixed 'not authorized' license bug




Changelog - phpPennyAuction version 2.4 
(compiled 01-Oct-2010)


Main New Features.
Integrated Stats tracking service
8 New Templates
Automated Web Installation script
New auction types: Beginner Auctions, MadBid (capped time) auctions, reverse auctions
Overhauled license method allowing for instant server changes, localhost license
Buy It Now updates, allow auction to continue and/or use up bids
'Tweet This' auto Twitter service
Fully 'Friendly SEO' links & pages
Improved server load and balancing (over 20x less server loaded used  compared with v2.3)



Other New Features.
Whole new, clean Admin Panel with help files
Single cron job to execute all others
Upgraded FCKEditor to CKEditor 
Vastly updated MySQL caching system
Annotated & commented code in multiple files for easy editing
Overhauled 'cleaner' system
Updated PayPal IPN for instant crediting/fraud checking
Bit.ly support for shorter URLs
Product deletion now instant, cached for restoring
Overhauled newsletter system
Facebook iLike support
Multiple image upload
Improved WYSIWYG editor
Refined template & file structures

...And over 40 bug fixes. 


Find out more at http://www.phppennyauction.com
